Guide to the Geoffrey T. Hellman Papers MSS.050
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize - Series 5: Onward and Upward
  - Onward And Upward With The Sciences: Galleys Peabody Museum, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Onward And Upward With The Social Sciences: Galleys Cyclopedia of Commercial and Business Anecdotes, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts Editorial Proofs Elizabethan Club, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts Editorial Proofs Post, Emily, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts Talk of the Town Regarding Emily Post Editorial Proofs, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts Rich Writers Editorial Proof, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts The Stuart Collection Editorial Proof, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Onward And Upward With The Arts, Department of Amplification Regarding American Philosophical Society Editorial Proof, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Onward And Upward With The Sciences Peabody Museum Editorial Proof, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Oversize - Series 6: A Reporter at Large
  - Galleys, 1933-1962 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Sachs, Alexander Galleys, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Editorial Proofs Talk of the Town, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Sachs, Alexander Editorial Proofs, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Oversize - Series 7: World War II
  - Galleys Hopkins, Harry Profile, 1943-1961 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Collier's Tearsheet Regarding Harry Hopkins Profile, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Galleys Morganthau, Henry Profile, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Galleys Casuals, 1942-1952 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Galleys That Was The War, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - En Guardia Tearsheet Undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Editorial Proofs Talk of the Town, 1946-1961 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Oversize - Series 8: Other Articles in The New Yorker
  - Department of Amplification Galley and Editorial Proof, 1955-1966 (Box Map case, Folder 4)
  - That Was New York: Central Park, Two blueprints of the Obelisk, undated (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 2)
- Oversize - Series 10: xsOther Publications
  - Holiday Reprint, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Life Tearsheets, 1938-1953 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Life Magazine Copy of issue 11/20/1939 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Life Magazine Copy of issue 2/25/1946 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Life Undated Charles Luckman Research Material (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - White Collar Zoo Advertisement Galley files, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Heritage Galleys Galley files, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Saturday Review of Literature Crowninshield, Frank Galley files, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Oversize - Series 11: Books
  - How To Disappear For An Hour, undated book cover (Box Map case, Folder 13)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour, undated dust jacket (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 5)
  - How To Disappear For An Hour, undated Promenade Review Galley (Box Shared Fales 079, Folder 6)
  - Betty Parson's Gallery - Steinberg Poster, 1969 (Folder 11 Right)
- Oversize - Series 13: Correspondence
  - Hellman, Geoffrey The New Yorker Christmas Poem, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Osborn, Bob, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Morgan Library Poster, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - PM Magazine, undated with Steinberg drawing (Box Map case, Folder 24)
  - Shull, Leo. Proofs from "The Gourmet's Life", undated (Folder 2 Left)